Guide to the Office of the Chancellor and Executive Vice President 1952-1966 RG 6.0
New York University Libraries, Publisher
- Series III: George D. Stoddard, 1960-1964
  - Subseries C: 1961 - 1962
    - Space - Warren Weaver Hall (Courant Institute), 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Special Projects, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Special Projects - Graduate Institute of Book Publishing, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Graduate Institute of Book Publishing, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255383 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Special Projects - Hall of Fame, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Special Projects - Puerto Rico Culture Center, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Students - Dean of Students, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Students - Foreign Student Center, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Students - Glee Club, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Students - Loeb Student Center, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Students - Rhodes Scholarship, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Television - NYU Television Production Center, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Television - College for Independent Study, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - University Health Services, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - University Health Services, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Worlds Fair, 1961-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255391 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Subseries D: 1962 - 1963
    - Administration - Assistant Executive Vice-President, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Administration - Assistant Executive Vice-President, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Administration - Board of Trustees, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Administration - Controller, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Administration - Radhakrishnan Visit, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Administration - Coordinator of Research Services, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Administration - Vice-President for University Development, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Administration - Vice-President, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Administration - Vice-President and Secretary, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Administration - Vice-President for University Relations, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255409 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Admissions, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Admissions - Scholarships, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Admissions - Financial Aid, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Committees - Conference on Education in the Sciences, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Committees - Faculty Morale, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Committees - Graduate Work, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Committees - Policy on Conferences, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Committees - Records Retention, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Appointments, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Faculty Prospects, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Government - Fort Bragg Visit, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Government - New York State Education Department, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Government - U.S. Office of Education, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Hall of Fame, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Housing Discrimination, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Library, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Library - Fales Collection, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Library - Tamiment, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255417 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Middle States Evaluation Committee, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Personnel, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Schools - Athletics, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Schools - Commerce, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Schools - Communications Arts Group, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Schools - Courant Institute, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Schools - Courant Institute, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Schools - Dentistry, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Schools - Education, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Schools - Engineering, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Schools - General Education, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Schools - Graduate School of Social Work, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Schools - Institute of Fine Arts, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Schools - Institute of Hebrew Studies, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Schools - International Affairs, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Schools - Law, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Schools - Medical, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Schools - Retailing, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255425 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Schools - University College of Arts and Science, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Washington Square College of Arts and Science, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Space - Catholic Student Center, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Space - Education, School of, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Space - Heights Plan, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Space - Library, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - Space - University Valley, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Space - University Valley, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Space - Warren Weaver Hall, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Space - Washington Square, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Special Projects - Peace Corps, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Special Projects - Peace Corps, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255433 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Students, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255441 (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Students - Dean John W. Knedler, Jr., 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255441 (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Students - International Student Center, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255441 (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Students - Medical Health Center Services, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255441 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - University Medals, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255441 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - University Press, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255441 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Series IV: Russell D. Niles
  The administrative records of Russell D. Niles measure 11 linear feet and span the years 1964-1966. The material has been processed into three chronological series representing each of the academic years of Niles' term, and a fourth series consists of administrative topics, Deans' Council minutes and mission statements originally set apart from the chronological series. The first series contains a small number of records from the final months of the George Stoddard administration. The third series, covering the academic year 1965-1966, was insufficiently processed by a student in the fall of 1987 and the finding aid to that series is not, in its present state, reliable. The excessive bulk in the Niles collection can be attributed, to a large extent, to the processing problems in series III. It must also be noted that the subseries on all- university departments in series II contains material spanning Niles' first two academic years, 1963-1964 and 1964-1965. Some files covering student grievances, the transfer of faculty members from one school to another, and specific faculty student relations are restricted.
  In relation to the previous subgroups, Niles' records contain a substantial number of files composed of material on spaces and buildings (most notably in series III, subseries IV), reflecting the many proposed and actual physical changes taking place at NYU at this time. A file on the President of the university refers to NYU's attempt to acquire the Worlds Fair Spanish Pavilion (Box 1/Fldr. 1) and the Astor estate in Rhinebeck, New York (Box 1/Fldr. 2). There are signs indicating the pending shutdown of the University Heights Campus and the subsequent need to strengthen Washington Square (Box 5/Fldrs. 6-7, 11-12; Box 6/Fldr. 4; Box 10/Fldrs. 16, 18).
  The files record changes that resulted from the Self Study Final Report and the Ford Foundation study, such as the upgrading of admissions and efforts to achieve increased centralization (Box 1/Fldr. 18; Box 2/Fldr. 1; Box 7/Fldr. 21-22). Mission statements (series IV, subseries III) demonstrate how well the schools and divisions meet the recommendations of the Self Study in planning their futures. Of particular interest are a series of files on "Project Apex," a program designed to train high-school students to teach in poverty stricken areas (Box 9/Fldr. 10; Box 14/Fldrs. 11-12). In addition, the first series contains a report on early experiments with LSD (Box 3/Fldr. 6).
  Niles was committed to building a strong central core around the arts and sciences at NYU, making undergraduate schools his priority. The files attest to his goals and movement toward centralization that the Office of Chancellor and Executive Vice President was largely responsible for promoting. Niles’ administrative records show him to be in touch with all aspects of University operations and demonstrates the growth of the position since the first years of David Henry’s term.
  - Subseries A: 1963 - 1964 (Includes Records of George Stoddard)
    - Sub-Subseries A: Administrative Officers
      - President, 1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - President, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Officers Group, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - Auxiliary Enterprises, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Vice-President for University Development, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Vice-President and Secretary, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Vice-President, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      - Vice-President for Business Management, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 8)
      - Vice-President for Business Management, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 9)
      - Vice-President for University Relations, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 10)
      - Institutional Research, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 11)
      - Assistant Executive Vice-President, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 12)
      - Treasurer and Controller, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
      - Coordinator of Research Services, 1960-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 14)
      - Coordinator of Research Services, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      - Coordinator of Research Services, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 16)
      - Administrative Council, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 17)
      - Dean of Admissions, 1961-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255003 (Box 26, Folder 18)
      - Dean of Admissions, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Dean of Financial Aid, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Dean of Financial Aid, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Dean of Financial Aid, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Registrar, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Sub-Subseries B: Administrative Subject Files
      - Alumni, General, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 6)
      - Committee to Coordinate Planning and Space Related Projects and Research, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 7)
      - Committee on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 8)
      - Committee on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 9)
      - Committee on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 10)
      - Committee on Coordinated Liberal Studies, 1964-1966; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      - Committee for Main Block Utilization, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Deans Council, 1961-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - General File, A-Z, 1961-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - General File, A-Z, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255011 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Government - National Science Foundation, 1962-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Government - National Science Foundation, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Government - New York Department of Education, 1962-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Librarian, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous Consultants, 1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Sub-Subseries C: Schools, Divisions, and Institutions
      - Executive Dean of Arts and Science, 1962-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Executive Dean of Business Schools, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Athletics, Division of, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - College of Engineering, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - College of Engineering, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - College of Engineering, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - Commerce, School of, 1962-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - Communications Arts Group, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255029 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - Courant Institute of Mathematics, 1961-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Courant Institute of Mathematics, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Courant Institute - Warren Weaver Hall Construction, 1961-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Dentistry, School of, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Education, School of, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Fine Arts, Institute of, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - General Education, Division of, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1962-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Graduate School of Arts and Science, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Graduate School of Arts and Science - Committee for the Selection of New Dean, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Graduate School of Social Work, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Hall of Fame, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Hebrew Studies, Institute of, 1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Law, School of, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Medicine, School of, 1960-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255037 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Project Apex, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Research, 1963-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Retailing, School of, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Retailing, Graduate School of, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Town Hall, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - University College of Arts and Science, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Washington Square College of Arts and Science, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Sub-Subseries E: Space
      - Space - Miscellaneous, 1961-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Space - Miscellaneous, 1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Space - Miscellaneous, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Space - University Heights, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Space - Washington Square, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Sub-Subseries F: Students
      - Dean of Students, 1962-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Dean of Students, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255045 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Foreign Student Program, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Students - General, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Glee Club, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Housing, 1955-1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Housing, 1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Loeb Student Center, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Religious Center, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Student Housing Facilities, 1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Tuition Increases, 1960-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Joe Weinstein Halls, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Subseries B: 1964 - 1965
    - Sub-Subseries A: Administrative Officers
      - President, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Vice-President, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Vice-President for University Development, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Vice-President for University Development, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Vice-President for Business, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Assistant Vice-President for Business Management, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Vice-President and Secretary, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255052 (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Vice-President for University, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Treasurer and Controller, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Assistant Executive Vice-President, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Budget Advisory Group, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Budget Advisory Group, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Budget Advisory Group, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Budget Advisory Group, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Board of Trustees, 1963-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Board of Trustees - Appointments, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Board of Trustees - Appointments, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Budget Coordinator, 1963-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Business Manager, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Officers Group - Minutes, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Sub-Subseries B: Administration Subject Files
      - Admissions, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Admissions, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Alumni Federation, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      - American Council on Education, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - Applicants, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255060 (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - Applicants, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Art Collection, University, 1962; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Athletics, Committee on, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Athletics, Division of, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Attorney, University, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Communication Arts Group, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Deans Council, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Financial Aid, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Financial Aid, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Government, General, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Government, NASA, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Government, National Science Foundation, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - J. Harvey - Consultant to the Chancellor, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Libraries, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - Libraries, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - New York State Department of Education, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Registrar, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Research Services, Office of, 1961-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255078 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Sub-Subseries C: Schools, Divisions, Institutes
      - Arts, School of, 1962-1963; bar code: 3 1142 042255086 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Arts, School of, 1963-1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255086 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Arts, School of, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255086 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Arts, School of, 1964; bar code: 3 1142 042255086 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Arts, School of, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255086 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Arts, School of, 1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255086 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Commerce, School of, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255086 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Courant Institute of Mathematics, 1964-1965; bar code: 3 1142 042255086 (Box 34, Folder 8)